How did we get here?
Debra, where you at?
I say how did we get here because I feel like I started this year as a different person.
I feel like I started this year with a different podcast.
And I feel like Small Doses has really grown over the course of this year as I stepped into a new phase of intentionality around this podcast.
That's not just with the topics and the guests, but also with the fact that we added this visual element to the thing.
And that was because I said, you know what, Amanda?
Like you already have something that's super dope.
You need to expand its dopeness and you need to take it to another level.
And I really appreciate y'all doing that with me.
I want Small Doses podcast to be one of these podcasts that people consider to be at the height of podcasts in terms of consistency, in terms of quality.
And you all continuously showing me that you care about it is doing that.
So thank you.